<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[David Cook]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[David Cook]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/david-cook/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 03:27:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/david-cook/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>That is one thing that traveling does, I think. It wakes us up and allows us to really feel things again. It takes us away from the day-to-day that sometimes starves us of our true emotion - of joy and wonder and love, and the power of these things inside of us. It is so easy to get caught up, and then to feel that we are moving through life feeling nothing. "Same shit, different day." Wandering across this world we understand again that we aren’t empty, but filled with life. I think that within all of us lies a desire to truly feel the power that we each have, and I’m realizing that it can only be found in the spectrum of emotions that we have been given to use as tools in this life. Perhaps this is why we read sad books and see scary movies. Why we ride thrill rides and watch romance films. But, there is something incredible to be found in exploring this world and finding these things for one's self. For it is so much more potent to be the hero of one's own story, rather than the voyeur of another’s. And that is what I’m realizing. If this is my story, then I don’t want to play a minor role. I don’t want to be a passerby or an extra. I want to feel! To laugh and to cry. To fall in love and to write a novel. To take on adventure with an open heart, craving interactions and experiences like the ones that I have had over the past few days. I want to be the hero of my own story. Even if it ends in tragedy, at least I stood up. At least I took on the monsters of this world and fought to the end. At least I learned who I was, and tried to express the tumultuous nature of my beautifully flawed existence. For, even as small as I am, I choose to live a big life, without apology. I will not be supporting character. If I have been blessed with the power to define this life on my own terms, then I will do so as the protagonist in this dramatic, painful, treacherous, incredibly beautiful world. And I feel so happy to have been given such an extraordinary setting for my story. What a world. I couldn't ask for more. </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/david-cook/that-is-one-thing-that-traveling-does-i-think-it-wakes-us/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2cccb7fa-e8d8-46b7-8ba5-cc1c9a84b303</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 03:27:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/14f1043a-086b-487d-abd7-fc355488ddb1.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/david-cook/0f6f6694-271b-479d-b613-07b06b83362e/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0f6f6694-271b-479d-b613-07b06b83362e</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 03:00:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>